Wasim Haider

Lahore, Punjab, Pakistan



wao.buzdar@gmail.com



+92-333-7407177



linkedin.com/in/wasimbuzdar

Summary

Hi! I am a UI/UX & Product Designer, i enjoy creating things that live on internet, My interest in user experience and user interface design started back in 2015, and i decided to continue working as UI/UX Designer. With the time i started understanding the user experience a bit deeply.

Fast forward today, i have had the privilege of working with tech giant, and startups, my main focus these days is building accessible, inclusive and digital experience at Edkasa for a noble cause of spreading education.

In my design according to user mind approach, where I make a connection between user and product, I always make sure that the product is Usable, Enjoyable, Equitable and perfect in usability.

Thanks

Experience



Senior UI/UX & Product Designer

Edkasa

Nov 2020 - Present (1 year 1 month +)



Sr. UI/UX & Product Designer

PayPro

Jun 2020 - Oct 2020 (5 months)



Sr. UI/UX & Product Designer

Roshni Rides

Oct 2019 - Jun 2020 (9 months)

I was responsible for all user experience and user interfaces designs here, creating the designs and prototypes of the products.



🌈 Sr UI/UX & Product Designer

FiveRivers Technologies

Mar 2017 - Oct 2019 (2 years 8 months)

I worked there as a Graphic Designer, UX/UI Designer, illustrator, video editor and as 2D Motion Graphic Artist...



📩 Graphic & UI UX Designer / Illustrator / 2D Animator

Ninesol Technologies

Jul 2015 - Feb 2017 (1 year 8 months)

Graphic Designer / Illustrator / 2D Animator at Ninesol Technologies Islamabad, Worked for mobile applications and websites...

Education



Bahauddin Zakariya University

Bachelor's degree, Graphic Design / Film making / Photography / 2D Animation and **Event Designing** 2010 - 2014

Licenses & Certifications



Google UX Design Professional Certificate - Google

Skills

UI/UX Design • User Experience (UX) • Web Design • Experience Design • User Experience Design (UED) • Mobile Applications • Interaction Design • Illustration • Short Films • Concept Development